Tonome?
You ready?
Yes.
Come on out, then!
Wow, looks grea—
Actually, it's just you in a high
school uniform instead of a suit.
Well, it's not as if you
can judge my age at a glance.
Akira-san is dressed like a student?!
That's somehow extremely adorable!
It's really not worth
getting excited over...
Your next investigation is
in a place frequented by students, right?
Yeah, and since you
can't eyeball his age,
he's perfect for an undercover operation.
It fits, though, and I think
it gets the point across.
Okay!
Then...
Next up, Kikira!
Daichi! Can I take pictures?!
I'm not cosplaying.
Man, you've got the vibe.
You'll totally fit in.
It sounds like both Kikira-san's
and my disguise are acceptable.
Well, that wraps up our prep—
Hey.
Who said it's over?
Uh-oh.
You haven't modeled your disguise yet.
Nah, I'm good! It's nothing
anyone wants to see anyway...
You don't get to say that
after putting me through this!
It's fine!
I tried it
on before I got here!
You sneaky little...!
Well, as long as it fits her,
I'm sure it's fine...
It's not a big deal!
Yes, it is!
What is Jarashi's outfit?
It's the uniform of our
next undercover target.
Here we go!
Moke-moke kyun!
Why did I have to dress like this?
What do you want?
The target we're after is a regular here.
They're not here yet,
but quit being shy
and maintain your cover.
I'm not being shy!
Hey, a new maid!
Your pattern's really cute!
Do your damn job.
I'm gonna.
Man... Plain fur is so nice.
It lets your outfit be the focus,
and it's so soft and cute.
That was so exhausting!
There, there! Well done!
The place was full of cute little girls
who looked great in their maid uniforms!
But Akira-san said you blended in
and got information about your target.
Well, it's not like
I wasn't gonna do my job.
I'm just not cut out for this,
and I know I'm not cute,
so it made me uncomfortable.
Well,
I don't know what you look like,
so I can't weigh in on your cuteness.
But...
You feel very cute to me.
And I'm happy I get to
snuggle your softness.
That's sexual harassment!
It is?!
Let me stroke your skin
and we'll call it even.
Isn't that sexual harassment, too?!
Anyway, let's buy clothes again sometime!
A real shopping spree!
Another girls' day out, huh?
So cute! It's another knockout!
Hey, this new one's cute, too!
W-Wait a minute!
The shopping spree is just for me?
Yeah, why?
I really don't want to
steal all the focus.
Why don't we buy things for you as well?
Hey, it's no big!
I love watching you try on outfits!
I'm not a dress-up doll, you know.
I'm a bit worn out,
so I'm going to take a break.
Please, enjoy shopping without me!
S-Sure...
My fur pattern is just so aggressive,
it makes it hard to pick out clothes...
The outfit's cute...
But if I wear it,
the two patterns will clash.
You can try that on, if you'd like.
I wouldn't like that, thanks!
Shizuka, have you ever
envied other people?
Envied them?
Like... people who can see?
I don't know what it's like to see,
so it never occurred to me to be jealous.
Oh, so that's how it works?
What about you, Jarashi-san?
I envy you a lot, Shizuka.
Me?
You're all one color.
One color?
So cute clothes look good on you!
I see.
So, Jarashi-san, you want to
wear cute clothing?
But I can't pull it off!
The maids and customers in the
maid cafe all said I looked good, but...
That's not what I want.
No matter how much everyone
else compliments me,
it's not the kind of cute I want to be.
The way I want to look is...
So I'll probably never
see myself as cute.
Don't laugh, okay?
But... I've been thinking
of dying my fur...
Bleaching out my pattern so I'm plain.
Sounds good to me!
It's not that easy!
Is it more serious than it sounds?
Well, my family line comes
from bobcat people in the Americas.
Our fur patterns
are proof of our heritage.
I was born and raised here, so...
I guess I don't owe
anyone anything, but...
I just remembered
something Akira-san said!
That's a fast change of subject!
Akira-san sometimes whispers his
thoughts about things he's looking at.
It's a full moon tonight. It's beautiful.
Why is the full moon beautiful?
Now that you mention it, I'm not sure.
Is it beautiful to have a round golden
ball against the blackness of the sky?
Which means...
A yuzu fruit on a bed
of nori seaweed would be pretty?
Why is that?
When I was a child, I was taught
that yuzu fruit is round and yellow,
and nori seaweed is big and black!
I see.
I like that, though.
That's a full moon night just
for you and me.
Just for Akira-san and me...
C'mon, Shizuka!
Don't get lost in thought
and giggle to yourself.
Oh, I'm sorry!
So what was it Tonome said?
Um... that's a secret!
Hey!
But it sounds like you're
feeling torn about it, right?
I guess.
Normally, when you make up your mind,
you don't need anyone's advice
to go through with it.
True...
I think maybe you haven't found
the answer you're comfortable with yet.
The answer...
So you probably don't have to commit to
"I need plain fur" or "I don't look
good in cute clothing" just yet.
What I mean is,
you may not really see your
pattern as flaw after all.
Y'know, we've got that in other colors.
Well, it clashes with my pattern,
so I figured I'd pass...
That's fine. It's possible
to make mixed pattern outfits.
A pattern on a pattern!
You'd be better with a cinched belt
and a color that matches your fur.
Well, maybe...
Take your time, now!
Can you believe this, Tonome-chan?!
No hugging, please.
Invisible hands are stopping me!
What is it now?
My wife's gone back
to her parents again!
Did she say why?
Her dad's in the hospital
and she has to look after him!
I see. How awful.
So please...
Let me stay here
until Light's back, please!
Why do you want that?!
I end up in a negative mood
when Light's not around.
I thought I could vent some curses on
your investigations like I did before...
But what about your shop?
It's shuttered for now.
If I don't vent my curses, they'll leak
out and affect all kinds of things.
Affect things how?
Just little misfortunes here and there!
So let me help until Light
gets back! Please, Tonome-sama!
I understand,
but how long will she be gone?
About five month, she says.
Oh, there's a deadline?
Which means...
Five months...
I won't get to see her
for five whole months!
Please calm down!
Five months?
Five months sounds like...
How do I look, Jarashi-san?
Is it all working?
Yeah, you've got it.
Hey, Shizuka, she's here!
Sorry for the wait!
It's been so long, Light-san!
Seriously!
Thanks for checking in, you two!
How are you doing, Light?
Just great!
Light-san, I heard your father
was in the hospital...
Is he all right?
Well...
He's not, actually.
The truth is...
I am currently with child!
Yes! I knew it!
Nice one!
Congrats!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
So why aren't you
telling Karma about this?
Well...
You know about Karma's dark
elf curse powers, right?
I'm a white elf, which means I have
the power of blessings.
Normally, our powers
cancel each other out.
But elves as a race have
a low pregnancy rate,
so when one of us is carrying,
they make a big deal out of it.
How so?
Once we know we're pregnant,
we spend time in the sacred elf
forest in the white elf village.
We perform rituals to pray
for a safe birth,
where the people spend every
day casting blessings on us...
and the elves in the village
support us every way they can.
The whole princess treatment!
It really is great!
But because the life
I'm carrying is so precious,
and if anything were to happen to me...
I know he'd blame himself.
He'd think his curses are to blame.
I know that would make our lives harder,
so I'm keeping it from him.
That's very frank of you.
But don't you feel nervous
without him around?
Well...
It's more that I'm worried about
what he'll get up to without me there!
I won't tell her that he
immediately went crying to Akira-san.
He stormed our agency in tears.
Oh, Jarashi-san...
It's getting rather cold
at night, isn't it?
What shall we get to eat tonight?
I'm craving something warm!
Hot pot!
That's that.
What kind of hot pot shall we have?
What about tomato hot pot?
I'd love that! Shall
we have it at my house?
Well, I'll cut the vegetables.
You wash them, please.
R-Right...
Is it all right for
Shizuka-san to use a knife?
Well, she lives alone,
so I'm sure she's fine. Still...
That's incredible!
What is?
W-Watch what you're cutting!
...Isn't something you
need to do, I guess.
This makes me really happy.
What does?
We've gotten closer
since we started dating,
and I've been able to learn
so much more about you.
I've realized something
about you recently, too.
What is it?
There's a smell
that I thought was yours...
You mentioned that before.
But I think that was actually
the smell of your suit.
Oh, my suit refresher?
Would you like to check my smell again?
Check... your smell?
Y-Yes, please!
W-Well, then,
so you don't confuse it with my
clothing smell... should I get undressed?
Well?
Y-You'd better not.
Shizuka-san, shall I add the pasta?
I'd better not drink too much soup, then!
That warmed me right up!
We have dessert today as well.
CUSTARD CREAM PUFF
Here.
What is it?
I-Is this...?!
I bought them while I was
at the supermarket.
I'm sorry.
Cream puffs are a problem for me.
I'm so sorry!
You see, when I eat them...
I end up getting ambushed by cream.
Yes, I can see that.
L: CAN WE TALK? - K: I CAN'T WAIT! VIDEO CALL?
L: I'D RATHER NOT. VOICE ONLY. - K: YOOOOOOOO!
KARMA
LIME AUDIO  CALLING
Hello! Is that you, Light?
How are you feeling?
It's gotten cold, huh? You keeping warm?
Five months is a long time, huh?
I can't wait to see you!
Really?
You're not actually angry?
Light?
I'm pregnant.
That's why I went home.
I have more resources here.
And I'm keeping other things from you.
B-But why didn't you tell me?
Do you remember?
When we got married...
Maybe we shouldn't.
You're backing out now?!
A dark elf like me doesn't belong
with a white elf like you.
Come on, we've been through this.
Maybe our parents'
generation had conflict,
but that has nothing to do with us!
Th-That's not what I mean.
I'm just not sure how my
curse will affect you...
Excuse me.
Do you think my blessing
power is worth nothing?
It cancels out your curse!
Look, I wanna be with you too!
But my curse powers are
the opposite of your blessings...
so I don't know if I could
really make you happy.
It's not your job to make me happy!
But if anything were to happen to you...
I...
You tried to run away because you were
afraid of your curse's effects, right?
I thought that, this time,
it might really be the end.
That's why I didn't tell you
about my pregnancy.
You'd just run away, right?!
I'm awful.
I didn't mean to say it that way...
I knew you were pregnant.
And yeah... I did try to run away.
BABY CLUB
ALL YOU NEED TO RAISE A HEALTHY CHILD
I won't run again. I swore I
wouldn't when we got married.
I'm sorry I made you
keep this to yourself.
How did you find out?!
Well, you said your father
was hospitalized,
so I got worried and called him...
Hello! Are you okay?!
Shut up! Stay away from my grandchild!
Grandchild?
Darn it, Dad!
And if you knew, why didn't you tell me?!
Well, I figured you wanted it
to be a surprise...
I didn't, you dummy!
Well, I'm relieved to hear
your parents are okay, at least.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
Hey, it's fine.
By the way, what was that other
thing you're keeping from me?
Wait and see.
Sure, I will!
Are you looking for something, ma'am?
O-Oh, not really...
I guess that person isn't here...
I'm looking for clothing
that looks good with my pattern.
Well, how about these?
How do you like it?
It looks great on you!
This is a foreign brand, so...
R-Right...
It's no good.
I just can't trust the
choices of plain-furred staff.
But the stuff I bought that day...
When someone with a pattern gives me
advice, I can let my guard down.
I wish I could talk to them again.
Excuse me...
Yes?
I believe you have a lizard-like
person on your staff...
Heya!
Oh, you are here.
I was handling stock in the back.
Were you the one looking for me?
Y-Yeah...
What is it?
Did I make you mad somehow?
I want advice on an outfit!
Hey, that's cool.
Let's have a look.
How's it look?
Showing off my legs...
My pattern doesn't get in the way?
Getting the right pattern
size balances it out.
But you've got such a great figure,
anything looks good on you.
That's not true.
If anything looked good on me,
I wouldn't need your help.
I'm Ako Mizunami.
My business cards, fresh off the press.
It's been my dream to open my own shop,
catering to patterned people.
So I hope I can count on your patronage.
Yeah?
I'll definitely have to support you.
I'm Luna Jarashi.
A potential future regular!
EPISODE 6: A PLACE WHERE I (YOU) BELONG
TO BE CONTINUED
Glad to have ya.